你们两个小棉花糖一踏上跳舞毯
When you two marshmallows first stepped up to the mat,
我就知道霹雳舞就是你们的需要的火
I was like "breakdancing is gonna roast them alive."
我也尽了严师的责任了
But I've been spitting a little knowledge to you two,
而你们也算是朽木可雕
and you all have soaked it up.
舞王玛蒂来了
Mix master Maddie in the house!
哦
Joey: Yeah.
玛蒂  你来干嘛
Maddie, what are you doing here?
迪吉  我意识到
Diggie, I realized that...
所谓情侣
Being a part of a couple
有时就需要爱屋及乌
means sometimes doing things that the other person likes.
所以  我和 Q 舞帝会过，他教了我一些舞步
So I met up with q-pop earlier, and he taught me a couple moves.
我觉着吧  不成功便成仁
I figure if I can't beat 'em, break 'em.
成仁不成那就来跳舞吧
Oh, and if you can't break 'em, breakdance.
说真的  玛蒂  霹雳舞可是 J 舞者和 D 大哥的菜  喔
Seriously, Maddie, breakdancing is mc j-town and dig-dog's thing... whoa!
来吧  Q 舞帝
Cue it, pop.
喔  就是这样
Oh, that's how I do!
就是这样
And that is how I do.
哇  好吧  乔伊  走起
Yeah, okay. Beat it, Joey.
我是说那个走起
The other "beat it."
知道啦
I know.